最好记录抽象函数
It's good practice to document the abstraction function
在类中使用注释表示不变量
and rep invariant in the class using comments
这就是声明rep的私有字段的地方。
that are right where the private fields of the rep are declared.
我们已经在上面做了。
We've already been doing that above.
另一份我们要你写的文件
Another piece of documentation that we'll ask you to write
是一个代表暴露安全的论点。
is a rep exposure safety argument.
这是一条评论，它检查了销售代表的每个部分，
This is a comment that examines each part of the rep,
查看处理该rep部分的代码--
looks at the code that handles that part of the rep--
尤其是在参数和返回值方面
particularly with respect to parameters and return values
从客户那里，因为那是代表曝光的地方--
from clients because that's where rep exposure occurs--
并给出代码不公开rep的原因。
and presents a reason why the code doesn't expose the rep.
下面是一个带有rep不变量的tweet示例
Here's an example of tweet with its rep invariant
从重复暴露中提取功能和安全性
abstraction function and safety from rep exposure
完全记录在案。
fully documented.
这是它的rep不变量。
Here is its rep invariant.
上面说作者是Twitter用户名，
It says that the author is a Twitter username,
定义了这意味着什么，它还说
defines what that means, It also says
tweet的长度小于或等于140个字符。
that the tweet is less than or equal to 140 characters long.
它的抽象功能是
And its abstraction function says
它代表了一条微博
that it represents a tweet posted
作者用文字的内容
by that author with the content of text
在时间戳上。
at the time time-stamped.
它有一个关于避免暴露在公众面前的安全性的论点。
And it has an argument for safety from rep exposure.
所有的田地都是私人的。
All the fields are private.
作者和文本是字符串，所以它们是
Author and text are strings, so they're
保证是不变的。
guaranteed to be immutable.
时间戳是可变日期。
Time stamp is a mutable date.
所以tweet构造函数可以得到时间戳，
So the tweet constructor can get time stamp,
制作防御副本以避免共享销售代表的数据
make defensive copies to avoid sharing the rep's data
反对客户。
object with clients.
现在，注意我们没有任何显式的rep不变量
Now, notice we don't have any explicit rep invariant
时间戳的条件
conditions on time stamp aside from
时间戳不是
the conventional assumption that time stamp is not
等于空，我们对所有对象引用都有空。
equal to null, which we have for all object references.
但我们还需要在广告曝光中加入时间戳
But we still need to include time stamp in the rep exposure
安全参数，因为不变性属性
safety argument because the immutability property
整个类型的依赖于保持不变的所有字段。
of the whole type depends on all the fields remaining unchanged.
以下是拉特南的论点--
Here are the arguments for ratnam--
它的代表不变量，它的抽象函数，
its rep invariant, its abstraction function,
以及它的安全性。
and its safety from rep exposure.
所有字段都是私有的。
All fields are private.
代表中的所有类型都是不可变的。
All types in the rep are immutable.
所以请注意，一个不变的代表特别容易争论
So notice that an immutable rep is particularly easy to argue
为了避免重复暴露。
for safety from rep exposure.